const STORE = [
  {
    question: "How many Star Wars ‘Episodes” are there? (pre Disney)",
    answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
    correctAnswer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "Of those ‘Episodes’ which is the first released?",
    answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
    correctAnswer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "Which (pre Disney) 'Episode' was the last to be released?",
    answers: [2, 4, 6, 8],
    correctAnswer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "Which ‘Episode’ does Lando Calrissian first appear?",
    answers: [1, 3, 5, 7],
    correctAnswer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Luke Skywalker’s father?",
    answers: ["Han Solo", "Ben Kenobi", "Darth Vader", "Admiral Ackbar"],
    correctAnswer: "Darth Vader"
  },
  {
    question: `“That’s no moon. It’s a space station.” What is this quote in reference too?`,
    answers: [
      "Star Destroyer",
      "Death Star",
      "Super Star Destroyer",
      "Millenium Falcon"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Death Star"
  },
  {
    question: "What planet was destroyed in ‘A New Hope’?",
    answers: ["Coruscant", "Tatooine", "Endor", "Alderaan"],
    correctAnswer: "Alderaan"
  },
  {
    question: "Which character made the order to destroy the planet?",
    answers: [
      "Darth Vader",
      "Grand Moff Tarkin",
      "Chewbacca",
      "Admiral Thrawn"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Grand Moff Tarkin"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the name of the bounty hunter who took Han Solo to Jabba the Hutt?",
    answers: ["Boba Fett", "Lando Calrissian", "Nein Nunb", "C-3PO"],
    correctAnswer: "Boba Fett"
  },
  {
    question: "When Lea tell Han she loves him, what was his response?",
    answers: ["I love you, too", "Shut up", "I told you so", "I know"],
    correctAnswer: "I know"
  }
];
